// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Up-to how many books does the bible have?",
    answer: "66 books",
    options: [
      "59 books",
      "66 books",
      "76 books",
      "60 books"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "The bible is divided into how many Testaments?",
    answer: "2 Testaments",
    options: [
      "10 Testaments",
      "1 Testament",
      "3 Testaments",
      "2 Testaments"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which one is the first book in the bible?",
    answer: "Genesis",
    options: [
      "Mathew",
      "Exodus",
      "Revelations",
      "Genesis"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which one is the last book in the bible?",
    answer: "Revelations",
    options: [
      "John",
      "Revelations",
      "Genesis",
      "Chronicles"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Genesis is about?",
    answer: "The beginning or origins",
    options: [
      "The end of the world",
      "The fall of the world",
      "The resurrection of the world",
      "The beginning or origins"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 6,
    question: "Who was the first person that God created?",
    answer: "Adam",
    options: [
      "Joseph",
      "Noah",
      "Adam",
      "Abel"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 7,
    question: "Which book is second after Genesis?",
    answer: "The book of Exodus",
    options: [
      "The book of Mathew",
      "The book of John",
      "The book of Exodus",
      "The book of Leviticus"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 8,
    question: "Exodus is about?",
    answer: "The rescuing of Israelites from Egyptian slavery servitude",
    options: [
      "The book tells tales of how the Israelites found themselves in Egyptian grounds",
      "The whole book is about the Egyptians",
      "The resurrection of Christ",
      "The rescuing of Israelites from Egyptian slavery servitude"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 9,
    question: "Who did God send to rescue the Israelites from Egypt?",
    answer: "He sent Moses",
    options: [
      "He sent Joshua",
      "He sent Moses",
      "He sent Jesus",
      "He sent David"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 10,
    question: "Who did God elect second after Moses to lead the Israelites?",
    answer: "Joshua",
    options: [
      "Joseph",
      "Solomon",
      "Jesus",
      "Joshua"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 11,
    question: "What is the name of the book that comes after Exodus?",
    answer: "Leviticus",
    options: [
      "Leviticus",
      "Numbers",
      "Deuteronomy",
      "Joshua"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 12,
    question: "Exodus has howmany chapters?",
    answer: "1-40",
    options: [
      "1-60",
      "1-35",
      "1-66",
      "1-40"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 13,
    question: "What is the book Leviticus about?",
    answer: "God gives Israelites instructions and guide for how to worship and praise Him",
    options: [
      "God gives Israelites instruments and tells them to sing and praise Him",
      "God gives Israelites instructions and guide for how to worship and praise Him",
      "God guides the Israelites at the desert by pillar of fire at night and of a cloud in the day",
      "God give the Israelites manna from heaven as they were hungry in the desert"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 14,
    question: "What is the book after Leviticus?",
    answer: "Numbers",
    options: [
      "Deuteronomy",
      "Joshua",
      "Judges",
      "Numbers"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 15,
    question: "What is the book of Numbers about?",
    answer: "Israel is failing to trust and obey God, and wanders in the wilderness for a period of 40 years",
    options: [
      "God gives Israelites instructions and guide for how to worship and praise Him",
      "Israel is trusting and obeying God, and wanders in the wilderness for a period of 40 years",
      "Israel is failing to trust and obey God, and wanders in the wilderness for a period of 40 years",
      "Israel is trusting and obeying God, and is on the right path to Cannan for a period of 40 years"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 16,
    question: "Which book comes after the book of Numbers?",
    answer: "Deuteronomy",
    options: [
      "Judges",
      "Joshua",
      "Leviticus",
      "Deuteronomy"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 17,
    question: "What happens in the book of Deuteronomy?",
    answer: "Moses gives Israel instructions and guide to love and obey God in the Promised Land",
    options: [
      "Moses gives Israel instructions and guide to love and obey God in the Promised Land",
      "God is angry at the Israelites for not obeying him",
      "Israel is failing to trust moses, and are not listening to anything he says",
      "The book of Deuteronomy is about the birth of Jesus"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 18,
    question: "What is the next book after Deuteronomy?",
    answer: "Joshua",
    options: [
      "Judges",
      "Joshua",
      "1 Samuel",
      "1 Kings"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 19,
    question: "What is the book of Joshua about?",
    answer: "Joshua becomes Israel’s new leader and leads Israel to conquer the Promised land.",
    options: [
      "Joshua runs away from the Israelites camps to avoid dying at war against Cannan inhabitants.",
      "The story of Israelites in the desert after leaving Mount Sinai as they reached the eastern boundary of Canaan",
      "The book of Joshua is about the story of David to be King over Israel",
      "Joshua becomes Israel’s new leader and leads Israel to conquer the Promised land."
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 20,
    question: "The book after Joshua is called?",
    answer: "Judges",
    options: [
      "Ruth",
      "Judges",
      "1 Samuel",
      "1 Kings"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 21,
    question: "The book of Judges is about?",
    answer: "Israel are turning from God, falling to oppressive nations, and rescued by leaders God sent called “judges”",
    options: [
      "Israel starts forgetting God and begin worshipping Idols, disobeying God's 10 commandments.",
      "Judges of Israel are againt God's ways and are misleading the Israelites out of the ways of God",
      "Judges is a book about the judgment of the Israelites in the wilderness by God.",
      "Israel are turning from God, falling to oppressive nations, and rescued by leaders God sent called “judges”."
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 22,
    question: "The book after Judges, is called?",
    answer: "Ruth",
    options: [
      "Ruth",
      "1 Chronicles",
      "1 Samuel",
      "1 Kings"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 23,
    question: "What happens in the book of Ruth?",
    answer: "Two widows lose everything, and find hope in Israel—which leads to the birth of the future King David",
    options: [
      "Two widows lose everything, and find hope in Israel—which leads to the birth of the future King Solomon",
      "Two widows lose everything, and find hope in Israel—which leads to the birth of the future King David",
      "A widow loses everything, and finds hope in Israel—which leads to the birth of the future King David",
      "A widow loses everything, and finds hope in Israel—which leads to the birth of the future King Solomon"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 24,
    question: "Name the next book after the book of Ruth?",
    answer: "Two widows lose everything, and find hope in Israel—which leads to the birth of the future King David",
    options: [
      "Ezra",
      "1 Chronicles",
      "1 Samuel",
      "1 Kings"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 25,
    question: "What is going on in the book of 1 Samuel?",
    answer: "Israel demands a king, who turns out to be quite a disappointment.",
    options: [
      "Israel demands a king, who turns out to be quite a disappointment.",
      "Israel demands a king, who turns out to be quite a great king.",
      "Israel turns down a king that would rule them rightiously.",
      "Israel demands to continue being led by Judges not a king."
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 26,
    question: "The book of 1 Samuel is followed by which book?",
    answer: "Israel demands a king, who turns out to be quite a disappointment.",
    options: [
      "Ezra",
      "1 Chronicles",
      "1 Kings",
      "2 Samuel"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 27,
    question: "What is the book of 2 Samuel talking about?",
    answer: "David, a man after God’s own heart, becomes king of Israel.",
    options: [
      "Solom, a man after God’s wisdom, becomes king of Israel.",
      "David, a man after God’s own heart, becomes king of Israel.",
      "Jehoshiakim, a man after God’s own heart, becomes king of Israel.",
      "David escapes and never to be seen again in Israel."
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 28,
    question: "The book of 2 Samuel is followed by which book?",
    answer: "1 Kings",
    options: [
      "Ezra",
      "1 Chronicles",
      "1 Kings",
      "John"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 29,
    question: "The book of 1 Kings is about?",
    answer: "Israel has peace and prosperity under King Solomon, but splits after, and the two kings turn from God.",
    options: [
      "Israel has peace and prosperity under King David, and remains faithful.",
      "Israel has peace and prosperity under King David, and remains faithful.",
      "Israel is at war under King Solomon, and decides to splits into two kingdoms.",
      "Israel has peace and prosperity under King Solomon, but splits after, and the two kings turn from God."
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 30,
    question: "The book of 1 Kings is followed by which book?",
    answer: "2 Kings.",
    options: [
      "Ezra",
      "1 Chronicles",
      "2 Kings",
      "John"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 31,
    question: "What happens in the book of 2 Kings?",
    answer: "Both kingdoms ignore God and his prophets, until they both fall captive to other world empires.",
    options: [
      "One of the kingdom ignore God and his prophets, until they both fall captive to other world empires.",
      "Both kingdoms ignore God and his prophets, until they both fall captive to other world empires.",
      "Both kingdoms obey God and his prophets, and they continue to conquer other world empires.",
      "One of the kingdoms obeys God and his prophets, and continues to conquer other world empires."
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 32,
    question: "The book of 2 Kings is followed by which book?",
    answer: "1 Chronicles",
    options: [
      "Ezra",
      "1 Chronicles",
      "3 Kings",
      "John"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 33,
    question: "What is happening in 1 Chronicles?",
    answer: "Brief history of Israel from Adam to David, with David commissioning the temple of God in Jerusalem.",
    options: [
      "Brief history of Israel from Adam to David, with David commissioning the temple of God in Jerusalem.",
      "Brief history of king David when rulling the Israelites.",
      "Brief history of Israel from Adam to David, with Solomon commissioning the temple of God in Egypt.",
      "Brief history of Cannan, the land of milk and honey."
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 34,
    question: "The book of 1 Chronicles is followed by which book?",
    answer: "2 Chronicles",
    options: [
      "Nehemiah",
      "2 Chronicles",
      "Esther",
      "John"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 35,
    question: "What is happening in 2 Chronicles?",
    answer: "Solomon builds the temple, but after rejecting God, Babylonians destroy the temple.",
    options: [
      "David builds the temple, but after centuries rejecting God, Babylonians destroy the temple.",
      "Solomon builds the temple, but after centuries rejecting God, Tesalonians destroy the temple.",
      "David builds the temple, but after centuries rejecting God, Babylonians the temple.",
      "Solomon builds the temple, but after centuries rejecting God, Babylonians destroy the temple."
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 36,
    question: "The book after 2 Chronicles is called?",
    answer: "Ezra",
    options: [
      "Nehemiah",
      "Ezra",
      "Esther",
      "John"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 37,
    question: "What is the story of Ezra?",
    answer: "Israel rebuilds the temple in Jerusalem, Ezra teaches the people to once again obey God’s laws.",
    options: [
      "Israel mourns over the temple in Jerusalem, Jehoshiakim teaches the people to once again obey God’s laws.",
      "Israel rebuilds the temple in Jerusalem, Jehoshiakim teaches the people to once again obey God’s laws.",
      "Israel rebuilds the temple in Jerusalem, Ezra teaches the people to once again obey God’s laws.",
      "Israel rebuilds the temple in Jerusalem, Solomon teaches the people to once again obey God’s laws."
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 38,
    question: "The book after Ezra is called?",
    answer: "Nehemiah",
    options: [
      "Nehemiah",
      "Job",
      "Esther",
      "John"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 39,
    question: "What is the story of Nehemiah?",
    answer: "The city of Jerusalem is in bad shape, so Nehemiah rebuilds the wall around the city.",
    options: [
      "The city of Jerusalem is in bad shape, so Nehemiah is crying to the Lord for help.",
      "The city of Jerusalem is in good shape, but Nehemiah destroys the wall around the city.",
      "The city of Jerusalem is in good shape, and Nehemiah becomes king of Israel.",
      "The city of Jerusalem is in bad shape, so Nehemiah rebuilds the wall around the city."
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 40,
    question: "What is the name of the book after Nehemiah?",
    answer: "Nehemiah",
    options: [
      "2 Nehemiah",
      "Job",
      "Esther",
      "John"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 41,
    question: "What happens in the book of Esther?",
    answer: "Someone hatches a genocidal plot to bring about Israel’s extinction, Esther faces the emperor to ask for help.",
    options: [
      "Someone plans to take over Israel and rule it, Esther is the one that knew this tyrant.",
      "Someone hatches a genocidal plot to bring about Israel’s extinction, Esther faces the emperor to ask for help.",
      "Someone plans to bring about Israel’s uprising, Esther is that person.",
      "The city of Jerusalem is in bad shape, so Esther rebuilds the wall around the city."
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 42,
    question: "What the name of the book after Esther?",
    answer: "Job",
    options: [
      "Psalms",
      "Job",
      "Esther",
      "John"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 43,
    question: "What happens in the book of Job?",
    answer: "Satan attacks a righteous man named Job, Job and his friends argue about why terrible things happening to him.",
    options: [
      "God attacks a sinful man named Job, Job and people are happy about the terrible things happening to him.",
      "Satan attacks a sinful man named Job, Job and people are happy about the terrible things happening to him.",
      "Satan attacks a righteous man named Job, Job and his friends argue about why terrible things happening to him.",
      "God attacks a righteous man named Job, Job and his friends argue about why terrible things happening to him."
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 44,
    question: "After Job, we have the book of?",
    answer: "Job",
    options: [
      "Psalms",
      "Song of Songs",
      "Proverbs",
      "Isaiah"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 45,
    question: "What happening in the book of Psalms?",
    answer: "A collection of 150 songs that Israel sang to God and to each other, kind of like a hymnal for ancient Israelites.",
    options: [
      "A collection of 100 songs that Israel sang to God and to each other, kind of like a hymnal for ancient Israelites.",
      "A collection of 150 prayers that Israel prayed to God and cried for help at the desert.",
      "A collection of 150 songs that Israel sang to God and to each other, kind of like a hymnal for ancient Israelites.",
      "A collection of 1000 songs that Israel sang to God and to each other, kind of like a hymnal for ancient Israelites."
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 46,
    question: "After the book of Psalms, we have the book of?",
    answer: "Proverbs",
    options: [
      "Ecclesiates",
      "Song of Songs",
      "Proverbs",
      "Isaiah"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 47,
    question: "What is the book of Proverbs about?",
    answer: "A collection of sayings to help people make wise decisions that bring about justice. by Solomon and other wise men.",
    options: [
      "A collection of sayings for people to make bad decisions that bring about injustice.",
      "A collection of sayings to help people make wise decisions that bring about justice. by Solomon and other wise men.",
      "A collection of 150 songs that Israel sang to God and to each other, kind of like a hymnal for ancient Israelites.",
      "A collection of sayings to help people make wise decisions that bring about justice. by Moses."
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 48,
    question: "After the book of Proverbs, we have the book of?",
    answer: "Ecclesiates",
    options: [
      "Ecclesiates",
      "Song of Songs",
      "Jeremiah",
      "Isaiah"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 49,
    question: "What is the book of Ecclesiates about?",
    answer: "A philosophical exploration of the meaning of life, with a surprisingly nihilistic tone for the Bible.",
    options: [
      "A philosophical exploration of the meaning of life, in a holly tone in the Bible.",
      "A philosophical exploration of the meaning of Christ, with a surprisingly religious tone in the Bible.",
      "A philosophical exploration of heaven, with it's wonders.",
      "A philosophical exploration of the meaning of life, with a surprisingly nihilistic tone for the Bible."
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 50,
    question: "After the book of Ecclesiates, which book is next?",
    answer: "Song of Songs",
    options: [
      "Lamentations",
      "Song of Songs",
      "Jeremiah",
      "Proverbs"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 51,
    question: "What is happening in Song of Songs?",
    answer: "A love song or collection of love songs celebrating love, desire, and marriage.",
    options: [
      "A collection of love songs written by Moses, celebrating his love for God.",
      "A collection of worshipping songs for praising, pleasing, and worshipping God.",
      "A love song or collection of love songs celebrating love, desire, and marriage.",
      "A philosophical exploration of the meaning of life."
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 52,
    question: "After Song of Songs, which book is next?",
    answer: "Isaiah",
    options: [
      "Lamentations",
      "Isaiah",
      "Jeremiah",
      "Ezekiel"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 53,
    question: "What happens in the book of Isaiah?",
    answer: "God sends Isaiah to warn Israel, but also to tells of a coming king who will “bear the sins of many.",
    options: [
      "Jesus tells Isaiah to calm dow and be less weary, but also to tells of a coming justice that will punish siners.",
      "God tells Isaiah to escape Israel, and tells him of coming times of hardship in Israel.",
      "God sends Isaiah to rule Israel as king, but the people regected him.",
      "God sends Isaiah to warn Israel, but also to tells of a coming king who will “bear the sins of many."
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 54,
    question: "After Isaiah, which book is next?",
    answer: "Jeremiah",
    options: [
      "Lamentations",
      "Daniel",
      "Jeremiah",
      "Ezekiel"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 55,
    question: "What is the story of Jeremiah?",
    answer: "God sends a prophet to warn Israel of coming Babylonian captivity, the people don’t take the news very well.",
    options: [
      "God sends a prophet to warn Israel of coming captivity, the people took the news very well and prepared.",
      "God sends a prophet to warn Israel of coming Babylonian captivity, the people don’t take the news very well.",
      "God sends Jeremiah to rule Israel as king, but the people regected him.",
      "God sends Jeremiah to warn Israel, but also to tells of a coming king who will “bear the sins of many."
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 56,
    question: "After Jeremiah, what is the name of the following book?",
    answer: "Lamentations",
    options: [
      "Lamentations",
      "Daniel",
      "Hosea",
      "Ezekiel"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 57,
    question: "What happens in the book of Lamentations?",
    answer: "A collection of dirges lamenting the fall of Jerusalem after the Babylonian attacks.",
    options: [
      "A collection of dirges rejoicing the rise of Jerusalem after the walls were rebuilt",
      "God sends a prophet to rule Israel and fight Babylonian captivity, the people fought side by side.",
      "A collection of worshipping songs for the safety of Jerusalem under God's wing",
      "A collection of dirges lamenting the fall of Jerusalem after the Babylonian attacks."
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 58,
    question: "After Lamentations, what is the name of the following book?",
    answer: "Ezekiel",
    options: [
      "John",
      "Daniel",
      "Hosea",
      "Ezekiel"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 59,
    question: "What happens in the book of Ezekiel?",
    answer: "God chooses a man to speak for Him to Israel, to tell them the error of their ways and teach justice.",
    options: [
      "God chooses a  group of man to speak for Him to Israel, to tell them the error of their ways and teach justice.",
      "God chooses a man to speak for Him to Israel, to tell them the error of their ways and teach justice.",
      "God chooses a man to train and fight for Israel in the battle against the Babylonians.",
      "God chooses a womam to speak for Him to Israel, to tell them the error of their ways and teach justice."
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 60,
    question: "After Ezekiel, which book is next?",
    answer: "Daniel",
    options: [
      "Joel",
      "Daniel",
      "Hosea",
      "Ezekiel"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 61,
    question: "What happens in the story of Daniel?",
    answer: "Daniel becomes a high-ranking wise man in the Babylonian and Persian empires, & has prophetic visions of Israel’s future.",
    options: [
      "God chooses a  group of man to speak for Him to Israel, to tell them the error of their ways and teach justice.",
      "God chooses a man to speak for Him to Israel, to tell them the error of their ways and teach justice.",
      "God chooses a man to train and fight for Israel in the battle against the Babylonians.",
      "God chooses a womam to speak for Him to Israel, to tell them the error of their ways and teach justice."
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 62,
    question: "After Daniel, which book is next?",
    answer: "Hosea",
    options: [
      "Joel",
      "Obadiah",
      "Hosea",
      "Amos"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 63,
    question: "What happens in the book of Hosea?",
    answer: "Hosea is told to marry a prostitute who leaves him, and he must bring her back: a picture of God’s relationship with Israel.",
    options: [
      "Hosea is told to marry a prostitute who leaves him, and he must bring her back: a picture of God’s relationship with Israel.",
      "Hosea is told to marry a princes who loves him, and he refuses: a picture of God’s relationship with Israel.",
      "Hosea is told to leave a prostitute who loves him, and he must be free of sin: a picture of God’s relationship with Israel.",
      "God chooses a womam to speak for Him to Israel, to tell them the error of their ways and teach justice."
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 64,
    question: "After Hosea, which book is next?",
    answer: "Joel",
    options: [
      "Amos",
      "Obadiah",
      "Hosea",
      "Joel"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 65,
    question: "What is happening in the book of Joel?",
    answer: "God sends a plague of locusts to Judge Israel, but his judgment on the surrounding nations is coming, too.",
    options: [
      "God sends disease to Judge Israel, but his judgment on the surrounding nations is coming, too.",
      "God sends an army to Judge Israel, but his judgment on the surrounding nations is coming, too.",
      "God sends a plague of locusts to Judge Israel, but his judgment on the surrounding nations is coming, too.",
      "God sends a man called Joel to Judge Israel, but his judgment on the surrounding nations is coming, too."
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 66,
    question: "After Joel, which book is next?",
    answer: "Amos",
    options: [
      "Amos",
      "Obadiah",
      "Jonah",
      "Micah"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 67,
    question: "What happens in the book of Amos?",
    answer: "A shepherd named Amos preaches against the injustice of the Northern Kingdom of Israel.",
    options: [
      "A shepherd named Amos preaches against the injustice of the Southern Kingdom of Israel.",
      "A king named Amos now rules the Northern Kingdom of Israel.",
      "A shepherd named Amos preaches against the injustice of the Northern Kingdom of Israel.",
      "God sends a man called Amos to Judge Israel, but his judgment on the surrounding nations is coming, too."
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 68,
    question: "After Amos, which book is next?",
    answer: "Obadiah",
    options: [
      "Nahum",
      "Obadiah",
      "Jonah",
      "Micah"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 69,
    question: "What happens in the book of Obadiah?",
    answer: "Obadiah warns the neighboring nation of Edom that they will be judged for plundering Jerusalem.",
    options: [
      "Obadiah tells the neighboring nation of Edom that they will be under Jerusalem's rule sooner or later.",
      "Obadiah is the new king of Israel and the neighboring nations of Edom.",
      "A shepherd named Obadiah preaches against the injustice of the Northern Kingdom of Israel.",
      "Obadiah warns the neighboring nation of Edom that they will be judged for plundering Jerusalem."
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 70,
    question: "After Obadiah, which book is next?",
    answer: "Jonah",
    options: [
      "Nahum",
      "Habakkuk",
      "Jonah",
      "Micah"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 71,
    question: "What happens in the book of Jonah?",
    answer: "A disobedient prophet runs from God, is swallowed by a great fish, then preaches God’s message to Nineveh.",
    options: [
      "An obedient prophet listens to God, then preaches God’s message to Nineveh.",
      "A disobedient prophet runs from God, is swallowed by a great fish, then preaches God’s message to Nineveh.",
      "A disobedient prophet runs from God, is swallowed by a great fish, then preaches God’s message to Jerusalem.",
      "A disobedient prophet runs from God, is swallowed by a great fish, then preaches God’s message to Israel."
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 72,
    question: "After Jonah, which book is next?",
    answer: "Micah",
    options: [
      "Nahum",
      "Habakkuk",
      "Zephaniah",
      "Micah"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 73,
    question: "What happens in the book of Micah?",
    answer: "Micah confronts leaders of Israel and Judah for injustice, and prophecies one day the Lord will rule in perfect justice",
    options: [
      "Micah congradulates leaders of Israel and Judah for justice, and prophecies one day the Lord will bless them.",
      "Micah confronts leaders of Israel and Judah for injustice, and prophecies one day the Lord will rule in perfect justice",
      "Micah confronts leaders of Jerusalem, and prophecies one day the Lord will rule their enemies.",
      "Micah confronts leaders of Jerusalem for injustice, and prophecies one day the Lord will destroy the city."
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 74,
    question: "After Micah, which book is next?",
    answer: "Nahum",
    options: [
      "Nahum",
      "Habakkuk",
      "Zephaniah",
      "Micah"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 75,
    question: "What happens in the book of Nahum?",
    answer: "Nahum foretells of God’s judgment on Nineveh, the capital of Assyria.",
    options: [
      "Nahum's sister foretells of God’s judgment on Nineveh, the capital of Assyria.",
      "Nahum becomes ruler of Nineveh, the capital of Assyria.",
      "Nahum foretells of God’s love for Nineveh, the capital of Assyria.",
      "Nahum foretells of God’s judgment on Nineveh, the capital of Assyria."
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 76,
    question: "After Nahum, which book is next?",
    answer: "Habakkuk",
    options: [
      "Haggai",
      "Habakkuk",
      "Zephaniah",
      "Micah"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 77,
    question: "What is happening in the book of Habakkuk?",
    answer: ".Habakkuk pleads God stops the injustice and violence in Judah, surprised to find God will use violent Babylonians to do so.",
    options: [
      "Habakkuk pleads God to continue the injustice and violence in Judah, and use the violent Babylonians to do so",
      "Habakkuk pleads God stops the injustice and violence in Judah, surprised to find God will use violent Babylonians to do so",
      "Habakkuk foretells of God’s love for Judah.",
      "Habakkuk becomes king of Judah, and stops God from using violent Babylonians to destry it"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 78,
    question: "After Habakkuk, which book is next?",
    answer: "Zephaniah",
    options: [
      "Haggai",
      "Habakkuk",
      "Zephaniah",
      "Micah"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 79,
    question: "What happens in the book of Zephaniah?",
    answer: "A disobedient prophet runs from God, is swallowed by a great fish, then preaches God’s message to Nineveh.",
    options: [
      "God says he will bless Israel and the surrounding nations, he will restore them with peace and justice.",
      "God warns that he will destroy Israel and the surrounding nations.",
      "God warns that he will judge Jerusalem.",
      "God warns that he will judge Israel and the surrounding nations, but also that he will restore them in peace and justice."
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 80,
    question: "After Zephaniah, which book is next?",
    answer: "Haggai",
    options: [
      "Nahum",
      "Habakkuk",
      "Haggai",
      "Micah"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 81,
    question: "What happens in the book of Haggai?",
    answer: "The people have abandoned the work of restoring God’s temple in Jerusalem, and so Haggai takes them to task.",
    options: [
      "The people rejoice while working to restore God’s temple in Jerusalem.",
      "God warns that he will destroy Jerusalem and the surrounding nations.",
      "The people have abandoned the work of restoring God’s temple in Jerusalem, and so Haggai takes them to task",
      "The people have abandoned the work of restoring God’s temple in Judah, and so Haggai takes them to task"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 82,
    question: "After Haggai, which book is next?",
    answer: "Zechariah",
    options: [
      "Zechariah",
      "Habakkuk",
      "Malachi",
      "Micah"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 83,
    question: "What happens in the book of Zechariah?",
    answer: "Prophet Zechariah calls Israel to return to God, records prophetic visions that show what’s happening behind the scenes.",
    options: [
      "Prophet Zechariah calls Israel to return to God, records prophetic visions that show what’s happening behind the scenes.",
      "Prophet Haggai calls Israel to return to God, and records prophetic visions that show what’s happening behind the scenes.",
      "Prophet Zechariah calls Israel to return to God, get's visions that show what will happen if they stop sinning.",
      "Prophet Zechariah calls God to bless Israel, for her good dids."
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 84,
    question: "After Zechariah, which book is next?",
    answer: "Malachi",
    options: [
      "Zechariah",
      "Habakkuk",
      "Malachi",
      "Micah"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 85,
    question: "What does the book of Malachi talks about?",
    answer: "God has been faithful to Israel, but they continue to live disconnected from him, so God sends Malachi to call them out.",
    options: [
      "Israel has always been faithful to God, but he continues to punish them, so Malachi prays for them",
      "God has been faithful to Israel, but they continue to live disconnected from him, so God sends Malachi to call them out.",
      "Malachi calls Israel to return to God, get's visions that show what will happen if they stop sinning.",
      "Malachi calls God to bless Israel, for her good dids."
    ]
  },
    



  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....
  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];
